

Gabriel Grad, Web Developer

VISEU DE SUS, ROMANIA · gabrielgrad94@gmail.com · +40744177737

LINKS

Linkedin

LANGUAGES

English

German

Romanian

SKILLS

Ability to Work Under Pressure

Teamwork Skills

Adaptability

PROFILE

Hardworking and enthusiastic self taught programmer with more than one year experience in software development, looking forward to continue my path in the world of Web Development. Particularly, my focus is on Apps Development and building Websites (Front-End Development).

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Junior UI/Angular Developer, P4B Group

Jul 2021 — Oct 2022, Cluj-Napoca, Cluj, Romania

- · Developed key features and maintained a large web application using Angular
- Defined and researched product features as part of the product team
- Designed and developed the Dashboard & Reports page for the customer-facing application
 by following an elaborate design process that included stakeholder interviews, user journey,
 low and high-fidelity prototyping, design and more
- Worked closely with BE developers, designers, project managers, etc. as part of an Agile team
- Worked on bug fixing and improving application performance
- Contributed on making the application responsive on mobile devices

Assistant Electrician, Private Company -Sascha Dörner

Jul 2019 — Jul 2020, Munich, Bavaria, Germany

- Transport tools, materials and electrical equipment for electrician
- Test for short circuits in wiring using multi-meter tests
- Fix or replace breakers in circuit panel
- Repair electrical equipment in apartments such as fuses, light sockets, bulbs, outlet and switches using hand tools
- · Experience in using one, two and three phase electrical panels

Production Assistant, BMW Group

Feb 2017 — Jul 2019, Munich, Bavaria, Germany

- · Assembles finished product
- Inspects product to ensure high quality
- Work as a Team Worked as member of assembly group utilizing hand tools
- Read specifications, design parts, build, maintain, and operate machinery and tools used to produce parts, and assemble the automobiles

EDUCATION

High School, High School Diploma Math and Info

Jan 2009 — Dec 2013

Udemy Academy, Full-Stack Web Development

Jan 2020 — Dec 2021

Build fully-fledged websites and web appsBackend development with NodeFrontend development with ReactLearn the latest frameworks and technologies, including Javascript ES6, Bootstrap 4, MongoDB.Learn professional developer best practices.

VHS - Volkshochschule, German Language Diploma German Language

Jan 2017 — Dec 2018

CERTIFICATIONS

Web Developer

May 2021 — Present

Udemy Academy

German Language

May 2018 — Present

VHS Learning

Electrician

May 2014 — Present

S.C Hexalina SRL

Digital Competence

Jun 2013 — Present

High Scool "Bogdan-Voda"